When we talk about movies with friends We're really recommending whether or not a friend should see
当我们和朋友谈论电影时我们真的建议朋友是否应该看
a movie that we've seen and they have not.
一部我们看过但他们没有看过的电影。
Right.
正确的。
We're giving reviews.
我们正在给出评论。
That's what we're doing actually.
这就是我们实际上正在做的事情。
So you need to know how to even if you're not a professional movie reviewer.
因此，即使您不是专业的影评人，您也需要知道如何做。
You need to know how to review a movie because again that's how you recommend movies.
您需要知道如何评论电影，因为这也是您推荐电影的方式。
You say what you like.
你说你喜欢什么。
You say what you didn't like.
你说你不喜欢的。
And sometimes it's more bad stuff than good stuff.
有时它比好东西更坏。
Sometimes it's more good stuff than bad stuff more positive or more negative.
有时，好的东西比坏的东西更积极或更消极。
More prose or more cons it's the same thing.
更多的散文或更多的缺点是一样的。
We can say often pros and cons very common.
我们可以说往往利弊很普遍。
OK so let's talk about some different phrases we can use when we're talking about movies we like or
好的，让我们来谈谈我们在谈论我们喜欢的电影时可以使用的一些不同的短语或
things about movies we like things about movies we don't like.
关于我们喜欢的电影的事情 关于我们不喜欢的电影的事情。
Notice that this is all mixed up.
请注意，这一切都混在一起了。
The thing I liked about the movie is my favorite part is the most memorable thing is can we say was
我喜欢这部电影的地方是我最喜欢的部分是最难忘的事情是我们可以说是
Yeah we can look at look at this one was terrible didn't make sense it was stupid.
是的，我们可以看看这个很糟糕，没有意义，它很愚蠢。
I mixed these up because often when people talk about movies they can use either the present tense or
我把它们混在一起了，因为人们经常在谈论电影时可以使用现在时或
the past tense.
过去式。
So in the story the main character is very very selfish very very greedy.
所以故事中的主角是非常非常自私非常非常贪婪。
He is that way or if you wanted to say it you could say he was really greedy in the movie.
他就是那样，或者如果你想说，你可以说他在电影中真的很贪婪。
Actually more often people will use is they'll use the present tense.
实际上，人们更经常使用的是他们会使用现在时。
And then when they're talking about their memory of it whether or not it was good or bad they'll use
然后当他们谈论他们对它的记忆时，无论它是好是坏，他们都会使用
the past tense.
过去式。
So you can kind of mix it up.
所以你可以把它混合起来。
It's all kind of okay.
一切都还好。
But usually when you're when you're talking about the story you kind of have to pick one and stay with
但通常当你在谈论这个故事时，你必须选择一个并坚持下去
it.
它。
So you should be consistent but it usually doesn't matter which one you choose.
所以你应该保持一致，但通常你选择哪一个并不重要。
And often again often when we describe the story the plot basically what happened.
当我们描述故事情节时，通常又经常发生的事情。
We use the present tense.
我们使用现在时。
Very common.
很常见。
OK.
好的。
The thing I liked about the movie is the action so realistic so fast paced so cool whatever you want
我喜欢这部电影的一点是动作如此逼真，节奏如此之快，随心所欲
to say.
说。
The thing I liked about the movie is maybe how real it felt.
我喜欢这部电影的地方可能是它的真实感。
That means it feels like real life.
这意味着它感觉就像真实的生活。
The thing I liked about the movie is how real it felt or how real it feels.
我喜欢这部电影的一点是它的真实感或真实感。
My favorite part is my favorite part is probably the acting the acting or we could say the performances
我最喜欢的部分是我最喜欢的部分可能是表演表演或者我们可以说表演
the performances.
表演。
You could say acting or performances.
你可以说表演或表演。
That means the actors or actresses did a very good job playing their characters or my favorite part
这意味着演员们在扮演他们的角色或我最喜欢的角色方面做得很好
is maybe a specific person.
也许是一个特定的人。
Let's let's use Kate Winslet Kate Winslet s height Kate Winslet s performance.
让我们用凯特温斯莱特凯特温斯莱特的身高凯特温斯莱特的表现吧。
My favorite part is Kate Winslet s performance.
我最喜欢的部分是凯特温斯莱特的表演。
You can choose a specific person if you want to.
如果你愿意，你可以选择一个特定的人。
OK maybe my favorite part is or my favorite part was the music.
好吧，也许我最喜欢的部分是音乐，或者我最喜欢的部分是音乐。
The soundtrack is amazing or was amazing.
配乐很棒或很棒。
The soundtrack is amazing.
配乐很棒。
This is the music that plays over it.
这是在它上面播放的音乐。
Probably the most memorable thing memorable means the thing you remember most.
最难忘的事情可能是最难忘的事情。
So this isn't always a positive thing but usually if something is memorable we're using it to describe
所以这并不总是一件积极的事情，但通常如果某件事令人难忘，我们会用它来描述
a thing that we think is is good is positive.
我们认为好的事情是积极的。
The most memorable thing is maybe the dialogue to see you could read that or write it up here D I A
最难忘的事情可能是看到你可以在这里阅读或写下来的对话 D I A
L O G you e which is what people are saying.
日志你就是人们所说的。
People talking in the story the dialogue is probably the most memorable thing in this movie or was probably
人们在故事中谈论的对话可能是这部电影中最令人难忘的事情，或者可能是
the most memorable thing in this movie.
这部电影中最难忘的事情。
Whatever it was about the dialogue very well written it stuck in your brain.
无论是关于对话的内容写得很好，它都会留在你的大脑中。
It's memorable.
这是令人难忘的。
Let's look at some negative things.
让我们看看一些负面的东西。
OK.
好的。
I thought the acting was terrible.
我觉得演技很烂。
So we use acting here.
所以我们在这里使用代理。
I thought the performances were terrible.
我觉得表演很糟糕。
Now if you use performances because it s e s then we have to say were terrible.
现在，如果您使用表演，因为它是那么我们不得不说是可怕的。
I thought the performances were terrible really not good.
我认为表演很糟糕真的不好。
Very all the characters were very two dimensional two dimensional characters two dimensional.
非常所有的字符都是非常二维的二维字符二维。
That means not realistic.
这意味着不现实。
So if we said oh so real so realistic.
所以如果我们说哦，那么真实，那么真实。
OK but if it's not very realistic then it's very two dimensional.
好的，但如果它不是很现实，那么它是非常二维的。
D I M E N S I O and l the story didn't make sense.
D I M E N S I O 和 l 这个故事没有意义。
The story didn't or doesn't make sense.
这个故事没有或没有意义。
That means if something doesn't make sense you can't really understand everything that happened because
这意味着如果某些事情没有意义，你就无法真正理解发生的一切，因为
all the pieces don't really fit.
所有的东西都不太合身。
Gather.
收集。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
The main character was at the school but at the same time there was another scene when he was at the
主角在学校，但同时又出现了他在学校的场景。
shopping center.
购物中心。
I don't understand.
我不明白。
It doesn't make sense if something confuses you like that because either you don't understand it or
如果某件事让你感到困惑，那是没有意义的，因为要么你不理解它，要么
maybe the writing was bad.
可能文笔不好。
Then you can say it doesn't make sense.
然后你可以说它没有意义。
If I'm speaking to you and what I'm saying is difficult to understand either because I'm not saying
如果我在和你说话，而我说的话也很难理解，因为我没有说
it clearly or because maybe you're very sleepy and you're not really paying attention.
很明显，或者因为也许你很困，而你并没有真正注意。
Wake up.
醒来。
You can say it doesn't make sense does it make sense.
你可以说它没有意义。
This is hard to understand.
这很难理解。
It doesn't make sense.
这没有意义。
The ending was stupid.
结局很愚蠢。
I don't think I really need to explain this one but you can talk about different parts of the movie
我不认为我真的需要解释这一点，但你可以谈论电影的不同部分
the middle the ending the part where so we can use the part where the part where and then describes
中间结尾部分 where 所以我们可以使用部分 where the part where 然后描述
something that happened the part where they went to the planet and saved the children was stupid.
他们去地球拯救孩子的那部分发生的事情是愚蠢的。
That part was stupid.
那部分是愚蠢的。
The rest of the movie I liked.
我喜欢这部电影的其余部分。
It was a good movie but the part where they where they.
这是一部好电影，但他们所在的部分。
And then say the action describe it a little bit.
然后说一下动作描述一下。
The part where they went to the planet to save the children.
他们去地球拯救孩子的部分。
That was kind of stupid.
那有点愚蠢。
So you can talk about specific parts or you can talk about something like the end.
所以你可以谈论具体的部分，也可以谈论结尾之类的东西。
You could say it was a stupid movie.
你可以说这是一部愚蠢的电影。
The whole thing was stupid.
整件事都很愚蠢。
That's OK too.
那也没关系。
It wasn't realistic it wasn't realistic.
这不现实，这不现实。
It's a realistic is similar to real real is actually usually used as a noun.
it's a real 类似于 real real 实际上通常用作名词。
Sometimes not.
有时不是。
You can say the source so real so real it's like real.
你可以说来源如此真实如此真实，就像真实一样。
So sometimes we use it that way but we often use this one instead which means like real realistic maps
所以有时我们会这样使用它，但我们经常使用这个来代替，这意味着就像真实的地图一样
wasn't realistic.
不现实。
Stupid bad movie.
愚蠢的烂片。
So these are some common ways we can express things we like don't like about movies and you can use
所以这些是我们可以表达我们喜欢不喜欢电影的一些常见方式，你可以使用
these for TV series.
这些用于电视剧。
In fact you can use these for books that you read as well.
事实上，您也可以将这些用于您阅读的书籍。
You can use these for a lot of different things when you're explaining them to your friends to help
当您向您的朋友解释它们时，您可以将它们用于许多不同的事情帮助
them understand why they should or shouldn't watch that or read that or whatever.
他们明白为什么他们应该或不应该看那个或读那个或其他什么。